What are you trying to do now?
You won't get custody anyway.
We will see that later.
What made us like this?
I wanted to live a happy life with you.
Then just give up and obey me.
If I see your face, I feel like throwing up.
You drank too fast.
Did something happen?
- Did you watch the movie that Suji is in?
- No. Why?
We had a fight about if Suji really
slept with her friend or not.
I think she did but Hae
Yoon thinks she didn't.
Why did you fight over that stupid movie?
- Is it because of Hae Yoon's ex boyfriend?
- Yeah.
She probably did sleep with him.
A man sleeps with a woman first.
Right?
So she did sleep with him, right?
Hey!
- I'm such a loser.
- Why?
Her past shouldn't matter, right?
It does matter but Suji sleeping with
her friend shouldn't matter at all.
You should've just agreed with Hae Yoon.
Really?
Fine.
- She didn't sleep with him!
- Hey!
Yeah. Please don't do that again.
I make 30 million won a year.
It's a lot of money.
I thought I could go to the top colleges
only by studying.
But you know it's
very hard these days.
It's even hard to get a job these days.
Why are you talking about your income all of a sudden?
So off topic.
That's because you don't know anything!
But it's the same topic.
Who is it this late at night?
I'll go check. Just sleep.
- What is it?
- Dad!
Hey. What are you doing there?
You're so drunk.
Let's get in.
- Dad!
- Why?
- I think you're amazing!
- What are you talking about?
How did you take all of this?
You take responsibility for
your wife, your kid and your social.
What's the life for a man?
Dad, I'm not very confident.
I'm not.
I didn't know how lonely it is to take responsibility for a woman.
I didn't know there are so many
things to do by myself.
What are you doing?
Jung Hoon drank so much last night
so I'm making soup for his hangover.
- I will do it.
- No. I want to do it.
- Did something happen between you two?
- Yeah. Something very good.
- What is it?
- You wouldn't know even if I tell you.
There's a life only men can understand.
Now I realize why many
fathers want to have a son.
Do they want a son? I thought
they want to have a daughter.
There are things only the
same sex can communicate.
When I was in a university hospital,
I made a group of only male interns.
I don't understand how a woman thinks.
I feel kind of isolated from you two.
- You have Hae Yoon.
- I'm going to go shopping with her.
Do whatever you want.
- Why did you wake up so early?
- I'm so thirsty.
- Dad is making you some hangover soup.
- It's done. Do you want to eat now?
Hey, go away.
He's my man!
He's my daddy! You go away.
No, no. Don't go away, both of you.
I'm feeling it now.
Hey, I want to talk to you.
You were so lovely last night.
I'm so embarrassed that I
showed you how weak I am.
It's better than pretending to be
strong while being very weak inside.
By the way, what makes you
worry so much?
It's my relationship with Hae Yoon
and money problems.
I think I can help you
with the money problems.
It's a list of wedding gifts
that Mom gave to Hae Yoon.
But Hae Yoon's family can't afford it.
I want to give what's on the list to Mom.
Do you have enough money
to afford these?
I borrowed money for that but I don't
think it's right. So I'm giving it back.
Okay. I will take care of it.
How are you going to do it?
Don't tell Mom about it.
Have you ever seen me yell or
get mad at her? Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for being honest with me.
I would've been mad at you if you
started your new life with a debt.
I'm glad you told me.
Once a man marries a woman, there are many
things that he has to take responsibility for.
There are many lonely moments
However, if you carry out your responsibility, your life rewards you
one the reward was you
I am lucky to have you as my father
I look sharp enough to present myself. Because of Hyeyoon, I have lost my confidence in presenting myself to woman
I am usually not like this
Hello
Hello. Your office is nice
Please come this way
Please have a seat
Would you like something to drink?
We don't need anything to drink. We've already had some
She's Hyeyoon's older sister
Are you suing your husband?
It seems like you have been negligent.
My husband is aware of the seizure, and lied about trying to push back the divorce on in order to prepare for the lawsuit.
Is he in a favorable place since he was the one who filed the lawsuit?
That's not true. What matters how much evidence there is, and how well you can defend your innocence.
And the other party's testimony is also crucial.
You sure do talk well. Maybe it's because you're a lawyer.
Mother, if you say that this much means that I talk well, then you're lowering your standards.
Of course we want someone who is good at their work, but what we really need is a lawyer who will treat this as if it was their own business.
That's difficult unless you're family unless you give me a lot of money.
But since you're Hye Yoon's mother, I'll pay special attention to this case.
It's a shame. If he wasn't married, he would have been a perfect Son-in-law.
Hye Yoon has known him since University. Why didn't she grab onto a man like him?
-Eh that girl...
-You think that would work out?
Are you going to stay in that house?
The one who can't win will end up having to leave. I won't leave.
Should I go and stay there with you? Then he would be embarrassed and leave, no?
You're also among the reasons for the divorce. If you stay with us, I worry he'll say you're meddling too much.
Him and me must have been mortal enemies in some previous life.
-Let's talk.
-You scare me. Where did you come from?
It's some talent. Running away whenever you're at a disadvantage.
That's why I want to talk. It's a little unfair.
Get out of the way.
Let's not do this. Let's go upstairs and have a tea!
Aunt, go see Dong Bi. I can't get in touch with her.
You're right on time.
-Let's take a photo together.
-Why?
You're acting weird.
Next to you I still have a long way to go.
What are you going to do with that?
It's a confirmation shot that I'm going to send to Mother-in-law.
Since I'm only apologizing in order to show Mother-in-law.
-You still haven't apologized.
-I will
-I don't lie.
-Then hurry up and do it!
I'll do it a little later. I need to build up to it.
What kind of girl acts like that?
100 million won has been deposited.
You were right, Hyung. This wasn't a good way to go about it.
-That cute bastard.
-Are you busy?
-No, come on in.
-Did Dong Bi contact you?
No.
She was with me at a restaurant and just disappeared after watching TV.
My Aunt even went home to find her, but she disappeared without a trace.
-She probably went on a trip.
-Would use leave in the middle of a meal to go on a trip?
Then she probably just went home. Isn't she from Busan?
I'm telling you she didn't go home.
It's small invincible Dong Bi. She has a habit of going into hiding. Don't worry.
You should be worrying. When someone disappears it's only natural to worry.
-You're pretending to be all cool about it.
-I'm not pretending, I really am cool about it.
That's just a defence mechanism after being hurt.
-Oh, you do know a thing or two.
-Of course.
What are you talking about over here?
Did you curse me out?
How could I possibly curse you out? Even in 3-cushion billiards the ball still needs to be in the game.
What's wrong with her?
Then why did you involve Mom and make your personal problem into a family issue?
-Are you blaming me for this?
-Sorry.
I'm the kind of person who points out the obvious. I forget that I don't have to do that with you, Chae Young.
Don't forget.
Come here.
I don't want to do this now.
-Why?
-You eyes were shifty. I felt like there was something up.
-What are you doing?
-If I was wrong just say so, why are you getting all angry?
I said that to make your smile.
If it's meant to make me smile but doesn't, then it's wrong.
A mop (sounds similar in korean)? That's meant for cleaning the floor.
When are you going to apologize?
♫ Thump thump, beat beat. What should I do? Should I hide away? ♫
[trans note: this is called an "apology song"]
♫ No, I have to muster up my courage. ♫
♫ I'm sorry. I apologize. ♫
-Sorry!
Now it's done, right?
-The apology.
-You haven't given me one.
They were the ones who said sorry.
I called them here so what they said, is the same as if I said it.
♫ No, I have to muster up my courage. ♫
♫ I'm sorry. I apologize. ♫
I'm sorry.
That looks funny. She certainly did apologize.
If I send this Unnie, she'll probably be really shocked.
Did you see the video and photo I send to you?
Looking at it, it seems that our Hye Yoon has done nothing wrong.
And she did all of this simply because I asked.
She's intelligent to think of something like this.
It's a little worrisome. Chae Young getting everyone involved over a small matter like this.
Okay. I'm hanging up.
Hye Yoon sure is praiseworthy.
Mother.
You're here. Were you flustered because I called you out of the blue?
No, mother. But I don't have a lot of time right now.
I have a schedule at a hospital later to receive some skin care.
Good. You have to take care of yourself so you'll look your best when you wear your wedding dress.
If you don't take good care of your skin it starts to show after you turn 40.
-Mother, you take good acre of your skin, right?
-Of course!
-Come here.
-Where are we going?
Because you're such a good daughter-in-law I wanted to buy you some clothes.
That's okay.
No, I'll buy you something so you'll beautiful at Ki Joong's engagement party.
Our relatives will all be there.
Come here.
Try wearing this. Dresses that follow the body line are more feminine.
It's pretty!
It's too expensive, Mother.
That's right. Because of you my wallet is so busy these days.
-Pick out some shoes too.
-No that's okay.
-They will do.
-Thank you, Mother.
Now I understand why men buy clothes for women.
It makes me proud to see so pretty.
If you weren't pretty it would be annoying to buy clothes.
But seeing you like this, I want to buy something too. Will you help me pick something?
-There you are.
-What's that? Did you go shopping?
Why? Am I not allowed to buy clothes?
Eh, Dad work so hard to make that money. Don't you spend it too easily?
If I had to buy it with your salary, your mother would end up looking like a slave.
He wasn't talking to you, but telling me not to spend our money like that in the future.
No way. Our Jung Hoon isn't that up-tight.
He isn't that smart.
You truly did raise me. How do you know me so well?
But are you angry with Hye Yoon. Since I told you that I was meeting Hye Yoon you worried for 3 whole seconds.
He didn't answer my phone last night either. Must have been on purpose then.
Last night he came home late with Ki Joong, he probably didn't hear the phone ring.
Then he could have called me today.
That can happen when someone's busy...
What am I doing right now? I lacked tact, right?
I don't think that's right, Mom.
That makes me upset. Why does an elder like me have to be so tactful?
I'm sorry, Mother.
In the last moment we should have talked, but she tries to kill me instead?
Hello!
Remove your bike from outside my house, or I'm going to break it!
How would he break it? That requires some courage.
Oh, so she's ignoring me, huh?
Fine.
I'm leaving first!
What's this?
Worry dolls. In the future they'll do all the worrying for you.
Then all you have to do is live happily.
Even when we fight all you do is think about me.
Even while being apart from you, I was thinking about what I can do for you.
Don't start crying because you're touched. And no need to scold me either.
You started it.
Try searching for it online. See if there's anyone who wouldn't care about his fiancee's ex-boyfriends.
Women are not the only ones who want to be reassured. Men are like that too.
And you hid it from me. That makes me even more upset.
If I had hidden something like that from you, would you just stand still?
You try searching online too. To see if there's any woman who could easily tell her fiancee about her ex-boyfriend.
9 out of 10 would definitely hide it.
I also acted according to the norm. So to be completed dismissed because of this is unfair.
So you're saying that I was petty.
I'm sorry Hye Yoon.
You know... They say it's nice to do it in a car.
Do what?
You are a filthy man after all.
Let's try it next time.
Start driving already. Brother-in-law will end up closing the doors while waiting for us.
-We really can't?
-We can.
Why haven't you gotten off work yet? Everyone else has left.
-You said your sister-in-law was coming over.
-She's my guest, so I'll take care of her.
Yes.
You still haven't left?
I told you not to come here. People are going to start noticing.
-There was no one around.
-The lawyer said to be careful doing the lawsuit.
Then how can we meet? If you don't want me to come, then you should come see me.
My sister-in-law is coming, so go for now.
-I'll step by later.
-I thought you said you were divorcing.
Why would your sister-in-law come here? You made up with your wife without my knowledge, right?
No.
-What is it? I feel uneasy about this.
-Let's talk later.
-Unnie stepped by.
-What Unnie?
-Your wife.
-Why are you only telling me this now?
You didn't even give me time to say anything.
-No one is here.
-Brother-in-law should be here.
-Brother-in-law!
-Yes, come on in. You're late.
Hello. It seems everything got off work already.
Yes, it seems best for me to do this myself.
Come on in first and let's see what we can do.
We brought the pecan pie that you like.
It's been a long time since I had pecan pie.
Have you wronged my sister in some way? Since it's your favourite she makes it really well.
There's nothing to treat, why did you come out?
-I want to get rid of my beauty spots.
-You don't have any beauty spots.
Here. They're bothering me.
Ah you women...
You have a few imperfections!
We better do some white dual-toning.
It's a laser surgery and the effects a great. You better drop by when the employees are in for that.
-It's calming too.
-Yes.
Sister-in-law you should step by with him too. I'll give you some treatment before the wedding.
-Let's go remove that beauty spot.
Sir, you need to give me the game fee.
Game fee?
Oh that's right, I completely forgot.
Let's go.
Where has he been playing games, for her to come here and ask for money?
-What are you doing?
-I'm letting you know that I can be also become a liability for you.
Don't uselessly give out treatments.
You've already made yourself recognized, so don't think of doing anything.
I'm going to do more in the future. Since I was following your wishes you thought I couldn't do anything.
See you later.
-Stay like this for 20 minutes and then I'll take it out.
-Okay.
I think you chose your man well. There aren't many men who would follow you here to get skin treatment.
Kim and Min attorney offices.
All done.
We'll see each other often this month.
Will you hold my hand and enter with me during the ceremony?
Why would you ask that of me?
You are the eldest man in our family.
Now that the wedding is nearing I realize that it's a blessing to have an older man in the family.
If you're going to pick me for that reason, I don't particularly want to do it.
You're going to protect my sister in the future and its a special day.
Then my marriage would also become a day for you to show off that resolve.
-Is there still more to do?
-We're all finished.
Shall we invite brother-in-law to go have something to eat?
-No, I have a prior engagement.
-It's late. You aren't going to go home?
Usually with this kind of work, it's busy at night too.
Brother-in-law, did Mother ask you to introduce her to Kim and Min's attorney office?
What?
No. Why do you ask about that?
A few days ago Mother asked me if I knew about any lawyer. Obviously I don't.
I saw the documents on your table, so I just wondered if she had asked you for an introduction.
Well, let's go now.
-He totally ignored what I said, right?
-Then do you want to fight over that?
I'll break it.
Deul Rae.
Does she think it's only her property?
He's not answering on purpose, eh? What's should I do then...
-Yes, Aunt?
-Do you happen to know where he is?
He isn't answering my calls. I'm talking about Min Ho.
I came out on another business, so I don't really know. Try calling him again.
How can I help you?
Do you have this in a different color? I wanted to get two.
Please wait a moment.
-What's this?
-Come in and have a look.
It's a present.
Two? One of them is for Cheo Hyung.
For her? Why?
Why?
This isn't right... It's what I expected from Hye Yoon...
Do you like it?
What happened? This was on the wedding list that I gave to Hye Yoon.
I heard from Jung Hoon, and since he doesn't have the means I did it for him as his father.
This isn't something Jung Hoon should handle, but something Hye Yoon should handle.
They are going to live as one anyways.
They face their problems together from now on.
So what? How long do we have to do everything for Hye Yoon?
Of course we have to help her. Because of circumstances, it's just for the wedding preparations.
-This is going to end soon.
-No! She's going to live off our son for life!
-Honey!
-Ah really...
What's this? Do you know what I've been up to today?
Do you know how much I spend on clothes and shoes for Hye Yoon today?
They're going to get married anyways, so the clothes...
I really can't let this go. Stop always looking out for Hye Yoon and look out for me too!
Deciding on the marriage with Hye Yoon, do you know how much that broke me?
I thought she was frivolous with money, but instead she's always calculating the prices.
What's this? I have enough bags.
I don't need this. Do you think I asked Hye Yoon to get this for me because I needed it?
A daughter-in-law need to give something like this in front of a crowd in order to be appreciated.
I especially wanted to show my sister.
But without even asking me,
She coaxed the task onto my son. You think this is something that will be solved by you acting as a good father?
I understand. I should have considered it more carefully.
Let's not overlook this. I can't overlook this!
Then what are you going to do?
Are you going to start breaking plates?
Do whatever you feel like. I've always matched your wishes.
But tonight you really make me angry! Is this all a man's life is?
Are you angry with me now?
-I don't want to be apart.
-Then let's not.
-Really?
-No.
My clothes and shoes.
I'll fetch them.
What are you doing here instead of going inside?
What are you doing?
I told you not to contact me. Why are you here?
Good evening.
Does it look like I'm having a good evening?
-Who's there?
-Jeon Sang Jin.
Come on in.
-What was that?
-I don't know.
-Why did you hit him?
-I thought he came to see me.
And you were here. And you've been sensitive about him...
And I thought you would misunderstand. Oh no! I'm so embarrassed!
-Why did he come here?
-How would I know?
-Ah I don't know. I don't think I can even go inside right now...
-Then I'll go in.
-Are you crazy?
-I'm curious as to why he is here.
-I want to go inside.
-Don't! It's late.
Still I can go inside. I'm this family's son-in-law.
What's wrong with you? What's wrong...
I'm sorry for calling you here so late.
It's okay. It's a good way to spend my time.
I got a new phone. Since I changed the Sim card, you can remove the number here.
The evidence photos and the statement are in here, right?
This is the memorandum...
This memorandum shows that the other woman would consider taking custody over the child, and it can be used in the evidence of adultery.
That's a relief. I was quite nervous when I received it.
You did well.
Can you have another one written about why she would raise someone else's child?
It's not like he is unrelated to this either.
-What do you want to do about this other woman?
-What do you mean?
You can also claim alimony. Do you want to process that too?
-Let's do that.
-No I don't want to go that far.
-Mom, please just go with me on this.
-Acting on a principle of morality.
More photos were sent to me than this, but I ruined some of them because I got too angry.
I'll talk with an expert about that. There should be a way to restore them.
Really?
So tomorrow I'll submit the evidence, the plaintiff's claim, and the memorandum to the court.
You have to prepare yourself for a tough time.
A divorce court is a petty and harsh battle.
And since you know each other well,
There's also bound to be a lot of personal attacks.
It's probably still better than marriage life, right?
No. Once the lawsuit is over and you have what you wanted that might be the case,
But unless you are fully prepared for the degrading nature of this, the doors of Hell will open up as soon as we go into the lawsuit.
I know that you're in there. Come out!
He isn't there... How could he do that to my bike?
-My flying rock.
-Did you name it?
Did you name it flying rock?
What kind of name is that?
Where is my flying rock?
It's here. Look well for it and you should at the very least be able to find flying rock's handlebar.
Can't we go faster?
Oh no...
You didn't believe I would really do it, right? If I say I'll do something, then I really do it.
I'm going to kill you!
Don't be like this. This is murder!
I'm going to kill you and then kill myself. I don't even want to live without my flying rock!
Don't be like this. It's all a joke!
-A joke?
-Yes. A joke.
How can I believe that?
I thought something had happened to you!
Are you crying? Do you like it that much?
Everything is a joke to you, right?
I've always wanted to do. Even if I die the world will still be the same foolish place.
Days passed by, and that's how I lived 50 years of my life.
But I get really miserable thinking about living like that for another 10 years.
But when I think about my motorcycle, I no longer think about dying.
I'm in control of where I want to go.
To me that's who flying rock is.
Me too...
No matter how silly I am. I am not the kind of man who thoughtlessly kisses a woman.
Of course I'm not saying that I love you.
I don't fall in love. When people fall in love, they get all weird.
Do you like alcohol or do you like me? Do you like games or do you like me?
Do you like your friends, or do you like me?
Liking alcohol and liking you is not the same.
Liking games and liking you is not the same. Liking my friends and liking you, isn't the same.
Why can't we coexist in love?
-Are you crying?
-I'm not crying.
I almost cried.
I knew you'd have some wounds. Since you got divorced twice.
Mean wenches. If they were going to leave like that they could at least have left me with a kid.
It's all falling into place. Everything you did suddenly makes sense.
Do you want to date me? If you want I'll date you.
I know you're in your menopause. I'll accept it all.
You're asking for a beating!
Ah really...
The wedding hall, make-up and the house are all set.
The wedding gift will be set soon.
It's going to be fine. Trust me.
OK. I'll trust you. Then the wedding gifts are set too.
-Our checkup.
-Do we have to do that?
Lets do it. We decided to be honest to each other.
I need to know if I can have our baby with this checkup
-You too.
-Can't everyone have a baby?
Out of 7 couples, one is sterile.
The probability is pretty high.
You're an only son. Your parents wants us to have a baby.
Okay. I'll make an appointment.
Sang Jin probably left by now.
Wait.
-Hello
-Mom.
Just answer my question.
Don't say who I am.
-Is there a guest in the house?
-Are we making a movie or something?
-Can't you just answer the question?
-There's one guest.
Your sister.
-It's so embarrassing to see them.
-Let them be.
They look good together. Don't tell anybody about me. Especially to Jung Hoon's parents.
Why is something like happening to such a nice kid?
Things are like this and yet you still worry about your sister's marriage?
I would like for Hye Yoon to get married and live well.
Good evening.
How old are you to ride on his back? Showing off in the neighborhood.
-It's fine. It's nice to see.
-Are you on your way out? Should I drive you?
No, it's okay. I came in my car.
-I met your husband today.
-Is that so?
We went there to get some skin treatment before the wedding.
What Mom? Did you say something?
No. It's late, you better get going.
-You forgot again, didn't you?
-No,wait.
-What is it?
-Mother-in-law bought me some clothes and shoes.
-They're in the car.
-You must be happy, Hye Yoon.
You're already receiving so much love.
Yes, I really love it. If our marriage is a smooth as today it would be great!
Don't worry, I'm sure it'll be like that.
They asked me to write a statement that I would raise Tae Won well, so I wrote one.
Now she's going to withdraw from the lawsuit.
Did I do something wrong?
Do you really not know what you did wrong?
She said she would just leave if I said I would raise the kid.
-Didn't she tell you?
-I'll go out first. You came out a little later.
Don't contact me until I contact you.
Don't ignore me. I'm not stupid.
What was wrong about writing a statement?
I don't feel reassured that I have to explain that to you.
Think carefully about how they used you.
I'm not interested in how she used me.
I'm interested in how you're going to use me.
Once you get the divorce, are you going to ask me to marry you?
I'm not going to get married again.
I'm really pretty, I have a nice body, I'm nice and I'm ready to do anything for you.
-That still isn't enough?
-My wife was close to being perfect.
I know you think that I'm meeting you because I'm not satisfied with my wife so you look down on her.
-But that's not the case.
-Then what am I?
Why are you meeting me? Are you just playing with me?
Where do women learn to speak like that?
It seems like those words were wrapped the same place.
-Hello?
-Unnie, it's me.
Nara?
You must have erased my number. It's Yoo Ri.
Why?
Did you fool me? You told me that you would leave if I wrote a statement saying that I would raise the kid.
My child is as important to me as my own life. I have no intention of separating with my child.
I believe in you. How can you do this to me?
And what did you do to me? Did you think I wanted to get friendly with you?
Don't calle me again!
They both as mean as the other!
Do they think I'll just quietly stand by and watch?
The wedding list...
The wedding list has been handled
How?
Did took care of it for us. He bought the things for Mom in our stead.
How is that handled? It's just creating more problems!
Do you think your mother is just going to let this slip? She's going to conjure up a trillion bedbugs!
My mother isn't like that.
You're saying that because you didn't see her facial expression when she realized how things were resolved.
Then what should we do? Do you want me to ask Ki Joong to lend us the money again?
No I don't want that. I don't want him to see us lame.
Then there's nothing to do. We're stuck with the bedbugs. Our parents are the only one who can afford this.
And it's only possible because the bedbugs happened before marriage.
Are you confident that you won't spill this all to your mother?
I'm confident in that. My father will keep the secret too.
From the outside it might look like my mother is wearing the pants in the family, but during the decisive moments my father takes the lead.
Mom?
Ah! You startled me!
Why are you sleeping in my room, Mom?
You were also waiting for me in my room last time.
-Son...
-Yes?
Have I ever hit you?
No, you haven't.
Thank you, Mom. For being understanding about the wedding list.
I'll really be a good son to you later on.
Who says I'm being understanding?
The handbag in the living room, that's the wedding present that father gave you.
You think it's enough if I just accept it?
Do you think I would be here if that was the case?
How come you can't even figure that out?
So what? You were waiting here to scold me and hit me?
How come no one understand what I feel?
I called her alone and talked to her. I told her that she only needed to take care of the wedding presents.
-And then...
-She doesn't have any money.
YA!
Mom, let her off. What did Dad say? Didn't he explain the circumstances?
That day when you had been drinking and came home late. What did you tell your father?
What did you tell him for him to take your side?
-I didn't say much.
-You talked about the difficult of being a man, right?
How did you know that?
-It hurts.
-Do you realize what you did to me?
You shattered my conviction that I would never have to physically abuse my kid.
How can something you get over that easily be a conviction?
You father yelled at me.
He has never done anything like that before.
Even though I'm this angry, he has done nothing to cool my anger and just left me here.
You're the one who left first.
Why does Dad always have to bend to your will?
Whose fault to think this is? How can you talk to me like that?
After letting go of your conviction, you're letting it all go.
Get out! I don't even want to look at you! Go and sleep with your father.
What are you doing there?
Your father is sleeping. I couldn't sleep on bit, and yet he is sleeping.
Don't be like that. Let it go this time.
This is all because of Hye Yoon.
Since she butted into our lives the peace I worked so hard to protect just burst into bits.
Do you have to go through with this marriage?
From now on, I won't shamefully hide you.
-Are you going out so early?
-I was going to check on the kids' excursion next week.
Why are you up so early?
-I couldn't sleep.
-Where are you going?
-To get the newspaper.
-I'll get it for you!
I said I'll get it. Go inside.
What's that?
-Did you see it?
-Do you think I'm blind?
My friend asked me to care for it for a while.
What friend?
The friend who helped you with the savings last time?
Yes, that's right.
-Is that friend a woman or a man.
-A woman.
A female friend who ride a motorcycle.
Why would a married woman ride a motorcycle?
Her family sure must be happy.
I'm sure she took good care of the family.
-It's yours, right?
-How did you know?
-Is it really yours?
-Didn't you ask because you already knew?
You're out of your mind!
I'm speechless! No husband, no children and no support to those younger than you.
Do you think I raised you through thick and thin for this kind of thing?
What's wrong with it?
You can't even get married. And you don't have any money!
Do you really have to do something like this?
Unnie! What's wrong with you?
Unnie, who are you to act like this?
Why do you think I live like this? It's because of you!
If it wasn't for me, where do you think your children would be living? What kind of sister have you been to me?
I came to this age while paying beenfits.
Now I'm sick and tired of it all!
Fine! It's all my fault!
Hye Jin getting a divorce is my fault. And you being like this is my fault too!
Unnie is getting a divorce?
The picture sure looks nice.
Without me you two sure look perfect.
Let's talk in a little while.
For the first time ever you got angry and yelled at me yesterday.
I want to forget about it quickly, but my guts aren't strong enough to talk about it.
I'm sorry Mom. This is my fault.
Whatever. Take those things back.
If this is how I'm to receive the wedding present, then I don't want them.
I know you worry about it, so I also don't plan and talking to Hye Yoon about the wedding presents again.
I can no longer watch my dignity be destroyed by her.
Mom.
When I was younger this was never the case, but that I'm older, do I have to watch you and Dad fight?
I would have been hurt watching you two fight when I was growing up.
I told you to go sleep with your dad. But how can you actually think of doing it.
Even when I listen to what you say I'm wrong.
You should have woken your father up and told him that I wasn't well.
Did I raise you like that?
Didn't I love you more and as much as your father?
Now you're both bullying me?
For the time being you can both stay in this room.
You go outside for a bit. I need to talk to your mother.
Are you sacrificing your food? Hurry up and eat!
Why didn't you tell you? If the lawsuit is in action then it has been going on for a while!
We didn't want to get a kid who is about to get married involved.
Since I didn't know anything I even went to his hospital yesterday!
Then just give a call to that lawyer to thank him. It wasn't even his work hours but he suddenly came here to get the evidence.
Where can you find that kind of lawyer?
Didn't know about that either.
You knew each other in school. You should have latched onto him. What a missed opportunity.
-Mom!
-Fine! I know the past can't be changed.
Anyways I'm telling you to do well. It would be nice to have a devoted lawyer in our family.
-What are you going to do with a devoted lawyer?
-It's someone to rely on.
Mom, how can you even eat like this?
The war has barely begun, do you think you can fight on an empty stomach?
If you starve yourself any time something doesn't go your way, you'll end up dying without even putting up a fight.
Ah, it's hot.
Oppa, about yesterday...
Oppa, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
What does it mean to live as a man? Do you regret the time you've lived with me?
I married you 30 years ago.
During 28 years we raised our child together.
When Jung Hoon gets married and leaves, then the two of us will be alone.
If we are to enjoy it, we need to adjust our lifestyle.
That's scary.
It's weird that you would be scared.
I'm also scared of many things.
And there a many things to be scared of.
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought I could carry the burden on my own.
Since I'm the head of the household.
But if we are to live the rest of our lives like this...
Then I don't think it's right by you.
We're a married couple. We've come this far because we love each other dearly.
To this place where I left all my worries, away from you.
Come here.
Not there.
So mean. How can you fall asleep without me there?
I can't win against you.
Let's not change. Let's live like we did at the beginning.
Can't we do that?
Let's do that. If that's what you want.
Instead, if you get scared then tell me. I'll protect you.
Here it is.
-I'm going to end up seeing it anyways.
-Then you'll see it when you see it.
They say I have a 1cm wide cyst in my kidney.
-What's a cyst?
-It's a lump. They say there's nothing to worry about.
-How did your ultrasound go?
-They say everything is clean.
Thyroid, epigastrium, and uterus.
Why did Jeon Jang Sin come by your house?
It seems like one of my mother's acquaintances needed a lawyer.
But why would he go to your house?
That person was in our home.
What did your mother say? Didn't she say anything after receiving the wedding presents?
I told you my mother will do what my father asks.
-You should take after my mother on that.
-Did she really just let it go?
Yes. How many times do I have to tell you?
Didn't your father say anything else?
It's the wedding present and something I should be doing...
My Dad doesn't worry about things like that.
-Call your father.
-Why?
So I can thank him. Hurry up!
-I don't have my phone with me right.
-Ah, right.
Then let me talk with him over the phone later.
But it's a little strange. What kind of acquaintance is it for your mother to call Jeon Sang Jin over so late at night?
Is it someone she's that close with?
You can turn off your interest.
Once more her words fall short when we talk about Jeon Sang Jin.
-Aren't you going to see Brother-in-law?
-I can go today. You go on your own.
How can I go and get skin care without you?
Then don't go either.
We even made a reservation, how can we both refrain from going?
I think I'm going down with a cold.
Okay, then you should rest...
Ah! There's something we didn't talk about yesterday.
What?
The woman we saw at brother-in-law's hospital.
-What woman?
-The woman who came to collect the game fee.
I've seen that woman before. She's a model.
Really?
That's strange, isn't it? He isn't cheating, right?
No, I'm just saying that the atmosphere was a little strange. I'm not doubting your brother-in-law.
Unnie. Where are you?
Under no circumstance can you get excited or angry.
This woman has not prepared breakfast, even once. And due to laziness, she didn't even get up in the morning to see me off to work.
That's not true. He's the one who had no interested in the household.
I'm telling that you cannot act like this. In a courtroom, you can never get into a fight over things like this.
Please remember that.
Understood.
She's always out shopping and spending money.
Our closet is full of clothes, shoes, and bags. There's nothing but her things in our closet.
This is driving me crazy. How can they lie about things like this?
You're doing it again. Again.
Since I feel wronged it just comes out on its own.
Do you know what it means to really be wronged?
To have your child taken from you, to pay these consultation fees with no means, to leave the house you've been living in and move into a rented room.
And have to work as a cashier in a convenience store.
This will be your reality when we lose this lawsuit.
Sit down your family and talk about the times you've been wronged and resolve those feelings. Don't bring them into the courtroom.
Please answer me. If you cry you might gain sympathy, but you won't win.
Especially since the people who practice law are more rational than emotional.
I'll keep that in mind.
Leave all the perplexing questions to me, your lawyer, and don't respond to the provocation.
Okay.
The recording is done, and the photos too.
Don't record with your phone. If there's is something you need recorded, then it's better to do it in a small recording studio.
Yes.
You were caught off-guard. But this should return your sanity.
It looks like he's being careful. Meeting in a hotel like this is insufficient evidence of adultery.
At home, work, and when he goes out for a ride, he doesn't meet up with any women.
He is meticulous. Now that the fight has started, he will use all any methods to win.
He has to, since he doesn't have anything strong like fraud to go on.
If we prove adultery, then it's game over.
Please don't worry. As long as you do it as we practiced, it should be fine.
Yes, I understand.
-Did you wait long?
-No.
Lawyer, would you like to come with us?
No, that's okay. I'm busy.
Aren't the two of you close?
I thought he treated us well because of you.
-Turns out he's someone who always works hard.
-He'll do well. He's very competitive.
What do you want to eat?
Aren't you going to eat anything?
You eat up. Should I get you some juice? Watermelon juice is good for digestion.
Why aren't you asking?
I don't know what I should ask. Honestly, I don't know what I should do.
You just needed to remain in the dark.
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you sorry?
There isn't a lot of time until your wedding, but I feel like you won't be the same with Jung Hoon because of my divorce.
Do you know what I envy about Jung Hoon?
His parents.
If we had parents who did as well as them, then our life would probably be different.
Keep a bright personality. It's not like divorcing is a crime.
Don't worry about me, and just think about doing well for yourself.
Do you think it'll go well? If things go well it's just a question of taking in the harness.
Why wouldn't it go well? Brother-in-law was in the one in the wrong.
Someone once told me this: the suffering I go through now are a result of my past mistakes.
It means that if you eat well now, you'll live well later on.
So I'll eat.
And live.
What's wrong? If you let it all go, you'll feel better.
Don't do that!
I just have to endure.